http://www.ihma.org/privacypolicy

This website does not support your browser because it is out of date Update Browser
Cookies
This site uses some unobtrusive cookies to store information on your computer.
OK
Policy
Privacy Policy
The International Hologram Manufacturers Association (IHMA) is incorporated in England, providing business intelligence, events and publications for the holography industry and we are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you. By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. You can always control the cookies being stored on your computer by adjusting your browser settings.
IP Address Lookup
Our company uses third parties to provide information about visitors to our websites. When you visit our websites we will record your IP address. This address will be matched against public and proprietary IP address databases to provide us with information about your visit. This information may identify the organisation to whom the IP address is registered but not individuals. In some limited cases, ie single person companies, it may be possible to identify personal data from publicly available ICANN data.
Website Cookies and Link Tracking
Cookies allow us to provide important site functionality so you don’t have to re-enter lots of information. They also allow us to remember what links and pages have been clicked or viewed during a session. If you have provided us with personal data (for example, completing a contact form), we may associate this personal data with other information. This will allow us to identify and record what is most relevant to you.
By using your browser controls, you are always in control of the cookies we store and access on your computer. More information on how to control cookies and limit personal data processing can be found at www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/five-top-tips.
You can view our cookie policy in more detail by following this link.
Types of Communications
By submitting your email address on this website you are consenting to receive the particular piece of information you requested, as well as allowing us to send you appropriate and useful communications. This includes, but is not limited to; invitations to our industry leading events, our latest assets (newsletters, reports and case studies) and offers on services. The information submitted may be used in the following ways:
to respond to your enquiries and fulfil your requests, such as to send you newsletters or to respond to your questions and comments.
to complete and fulfil your purchase, for example, to process your payments, have your order delivered to you, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related customer service.
to provide you with updates and announcements concerning our products within the industry you have selected as your preference and to send you invitations to relevant events.
if you are an IHMA member, in order to fulfil your requests, information may be passed to the Hologram Image Register, managed by the Counterfeit Intelligence Bureau, who may send emails relevant to your submission.
to personalise your experience on the Sites by presenting products tailored to you.
for our business purposes, such as analysing and managing our businesses, market research, audits, enhancing our Sites, improving our services and products, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our campaigns, tailoring the Sites experience and content, gauging customer satisfaction and providing customer service (including troubleshooting in connection with customer issues).
as we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to enforce our terms and conditions.
At any time, you can update your preferences by clicking the link in any emails you receive from us. The link will always be in the footer of the email. You can also stop receiving emails from us using that same link. If you don’t have an email from us to hand and want to update your preferences, you can fill in the form below. We will send you an email for you to change your preferences as you wish.
Alternatively, you can call us, write to us or email us to let us know that you no longer wish to receive communications. We will always endeavour to make these changes within 48 hours, but on occasion with direct mail, the changes may take slightly longer to take effect.
Information Collected
We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.
Information Use
We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. Data collected in the UK is held in accordance with the Data Protection Act. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorised access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.
Cookies
Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files – “Cookies” – that hold information which allows a website to recognise you as a user. Our websites take advantage of this facility to enhance your experience. We use a number of these cookies for analytical purposes, and these are described in detail below. By using the following websites, you consent to the use of cookies for these purposes:
• www.ihma.org
We use a combination of both session and persistent cookies. Session cookies keep track of your current visit and how you navigate the site, persistent cookies enable our website to recognise you as a repeat visitor when you return. The session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will be removed on a pre-determined expiry date, or when deleted by you.
Most web browsers allow user privacy settings to block either all cookies, or third party cookies. Blocking cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one. Please visit www.aboutcookies.org for comprehensive information on how to change your cookie settings in a wide variety of different web browsers.
Google Analytics Cookies
Google Analytics is a website monitoring tool that allows users to see volumes of website visitors, their source, and to analyse how the content of their website is viewed and navigated. This in turn allows optimisation of the content and pages across our websites and the marketing programs that drive traffic to the website. Google Analytics does not store any personal information about website visitors, but does use persistent cookies to identify repeat visitors. You may universally opt-out of all Google Analytics tracking used by all websites by visiting the following url – https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Lead Tracking Cookies
We use a tool called GatorLeads to identify the business or organisation that website visitors belong to, based on a reverse IP Lookup. GatorLeads also use cookies to process this identification, and personal information about individual users is stored. Cookies used by GatorLeads store information about your current web browsing session (pages viewed, time on site etc) and the dates and times of previous website visits.
This information is used by the IHMA to profile website visitors, in order to better understand the way in which our website content is viewed by different industry segments. It is also used to identify the types of organisations that might be interested in subscribing to our Newsletters and attending our events.
Email Marketing Post-Click Tracking Cookies
These cookies are used to report on the pages of our website that have been viewed by visitors who have followed links from our email marketing campaigns. This analysis helps us to understand additional content that is viewed by the contacts in our database and therefore allows us to improve and tailor future campaigns to those contact’s specific areas of interest.
Below we list the different types of cookies that may be used on the site:
ESSENTIAL COOKIES
Essential cookies are necessary for the Site to work and enable you to move around it and to use its services and features. Without these absolutely necessary cookies, the Site will not perform as smoothly for you as we would like it to and we may not be able to provide the Site or certain services or features you request.
Cookie type
Description
How to manage cookies
Session
Session cookies are used to maintain the state of the application, for example when filling in a two-stage form.
Accept/refuse via browser setting
User ID
User ID cookies are used to ensure that users only see their own information.
Accept/refuse via browser setting
PREFERENCE COOKIES
Preference cookies collect information about your choices and preferences, and allow us to remember language or other local settings and customise the Site accordingly.
Cookie type
Description
How to manage cookies
Language
Language cookies are used to store the language the user has selected, and to show the correct options.
Accept/refuse via browser setting
Location
The user’s approximate address (city, state, country, postal code) as determined by the IP address is retained in order to automatically select the proper country.
Accept/refuse via browser setting
Reference site
The reference site is recorded to better understand the user’s preferences.
Accept/refuse via browser setting
Last visit and activity
Date of last visit and activity and other information is recorded to be able to better understand the user’s preferences.
Accept/refuse via browser setting
Page history
Page history cookies are used to track the sequence of pages the user has visited to allow us to improve our website experience.
Accept/refuse via browser setting
ANALYTICS COOKIES
Analytics cookies collect information about your use of the Site, and enable us to improve the way it works. For example, analytics cookies show us which are the most frequently visited pages on the Site, help us record any difficulties you have with the Site, and show us whether our campaigns are effective or not. This allows us to see the overall patterns of usage on the Site, rather than the usage of a single person.
Cookie Type
Description
How to manage cookies
Google analytics
Google analytics cookies collect aggregate statistical data to improve Site presentation and navigation.
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
MARKETING COOKIES
These cookies are used for marketing purposes.
Cookie Type
Description
How to manage cookies
Market analysis
Conduct market analysis
Accept/refuse via browser setting
Campaign / promotion
Measure effectiveness of campaign
Accept/refuse via browser setting
Disclosing Information
We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties except when we need to do so in order to complete the transaction – e.g. when arranging for delivery of goods that you have ordered. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent.
We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties – for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.
Changes to this Policy
Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document regularly to ensure that it still meets with your approval.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at info@ihma.org. You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details form any list under our control.
Home
About Us
Benefits
How To Join
Hologram Image Register
IHMA Officers
Code of Practice
Projects
